// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q016: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: '------ the necessary parts arrive today, the production of Model 501 will have to be postponed.',
      choices: ['Whenever', 'Without', 'Unless', 'In case'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Unless'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q151',
    },
    {
      question: 'The preservation of the ------ building is being actively discussed at a Keegan City Commission meeting set up last month.',
      choices: ['historic', 'historically', 'history', 'historian'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['historic'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q152',
    },
    {
      question: 'By the end of next month, Taiyo Financial Group must decide ------ it will open a branch in Hong Kong.',
      choices: ['but', 'because', 'although', 'whether'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['whether'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q153',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Singh left the office ------ after the monthly meeting to go on a business trip to Chicago.',
      choices: ['heavily', 'steadily', 'immediately', 'commonly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['immediately'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q154',
    },
    {
      question: 'As a ------ of our appreciation, we will be giving away free towels at this weekend’s sale.',
      choices: ['flyer', 'prescription', 'nomination', 'token'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['token'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q155',
    },
    {
      question: 'Arika Kitchen has earned a reputation for ------ and creative cuisine using ingredients from around the world.',
      choices: ['innovation', 'innovate', 'innovatively', 'innovative'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['innovative'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q156',
    },
    {
      question: 'Kevin Miyata ------ director of marketing because of his past performance recognized by the board of directors.',
      choices: ['appointing', 'was appointed', 'to be appointed', 'appoint'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['was appointed'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q157',
    },
    {
      question: 'Merrywood Supermarket introduced a loyalty points system last year to ------ customer satisfaction.',
      choices: ['enhance', 'attach', 'prescribe', 'expire'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['enhance'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q158',
    },
    {
      question: 'Visitors to the factory are asked to borrow ------ glasses from the reception desk and wear them at all times.',
      choices: ['protects', 'protective', 'protect', 'protectively'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['protective'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q159',
    },
    {
      question: 'Enzo Botanical Garden is ------ walking distance of the South Hillwood subway station on the East-West Line.',
      choices: ['next to', 'through', 'within', 'from'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['within'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題151-160/#q160',
    },
  ],
}